I wanna dance with you, forever
I wanna poke fun and play, forever
This sucks so bad, this countdown to bye-bye
not long now till it runs out, Fxxk
Hey, take me with you to the other side
“together forever” like on a playground, laugh around
But seriously, what's up with my wish not coming true Fxxk
You never ran out of love, I could always go back for seconds
there's nobody like you
I'm sorry for all my left-overs
if I could do it all over, I'd for sure clear my plate
I'm melting! Feelin' a bit blue as I avoid a sunburn
thinkin' real hard before I hit that @ mention
I'm cryin' on the inside, oh the things I wanted to tell you
now I'll never have that chance
Everything I thought I did for you, it was actually all for me
To realize that now, I mean, how thick am I?
Here, take all of my oxygen
so in exchange, please please wake up
I wanna dance with you, forever
I wanna poke fun and play, forever
This sucks so bad, this countdown to bye-bye
not long now till it runs out, Fxxk
Hey, take me with you to the other side
“together forever” like on a playground, laugh around
But seriously, what's up with my wish not coming true Fxxk
The other side of LOVE is still LOVE, there's no relief
my future's so bleak
I turn the back of my eyelids into a movie screen
showing snapshots of our memories
My tears blur the images
and I wonder, is this how memories fade?
Will I ever get over you?
What would you wish for, I wonder?
I want to move on
I want to close this chapter
I wanted to dance with you, forever
I wanted for us to poke fun and play, forever
The best days of our lives are coming to an end
not long now till it runs out, Fxxk
Hey, I can't go with you to the other side
“together forever” can't keep that promise
So sorry for leaving you solo
Cuz I want to remember forever
cuz I don't want to forget a thing
It's okay, you can laugh and call me a sap
let me wallow, Fxxk
If we meet again on the other side
“together forever” like on a playground, laugh around
Please break this spell you've cast on me Fxxk
The time I'll spend with somebody else
it's basically all dead rubber
The disease that kills euphoria and butterflies
only you know the cure
If we meet again on the other side
“together forever” like on a playground, laugh around
Please break this spell you've cast on me Fxxk
Official Translation
Subtitles: Feiyangjun_